I must bring you back and bring you back to life.
Shan Cha!
Shan Cha! Shan Cha!
I can't believe how powerful Li Piao is!
I must avenge you!
You risked your life for a drop of water!
I finally got you!
I must break Li Piao into pieces!
His name is Jin Da Xiong.
He is the reincarnation of the star of the universe.
He possesses the power of super power.
You must feel that Li Piao is about to disappear.
I won't hide from him.
You must know that the most powerful power in the world...
is the power of super power.
Li Piao!
You have been hit by Da Xiong's super power.
Although your life is in danger,
you must possess the power of super power...
in order to defeat the demons.
I will give you the power of super power.
You must step on the seven stars and enter the forest.
Now, focus on the seven stars.
The power of super power will enter your body.
Shan Cha!
I can't avenge you!
I can't get rid of Li Piao!
Shan Cha!
You used to be very brave.
I couldn't get rid of you.
I didn't expect that I could get rid of you.
But you've become like this.
Shan Cha!
If you want to die, then go ahead.
I don't want to waste my life.
Who are you to stop me from killing myself?
I'm Shan Cha's brother, Jin Da Xiong.
My brother needs your care.
So you can't die yet.
I hate that I can't save him.
I don't want to live anymore.
I will save him.
But I need to change his mind.
Change his mind?
Yes, change his mind.
If he changes his mind,
what if he doesn't want to talk to me anymore?
I will go to Li Piao's girlfriend.
Li Piao!
What is it?
I want to tell you that Li Na is in danger.
Come up.
I can't. You come down.
She's just a girl. Why are you afraid of her?
You're right.
But you're very good at martial arts.
What martial arts do you want to learn?
I want to learn how to use the invisible technique.
Okay, pay attention.
Good.
You're really good.
Stand up.
Okay.
Watch my performance.
I'm changing.
Why are you acting like a child?
I just want to tell you that you can't use the invisible technique.
You didn't tell me about the invisible technique.
He's too young. What kind of martial arts do you want to learn?
I'll show you another kind of martial arts.
Poor thing.
You saw the death of Zhao Xin.
He's a traitor.
Run!
Hurry up.
I'll show you the power of death.
I think there was a power outage just now.
The invisible technique.
Xin can't be used anymore.
Li Wei!
The blood has been stained red.
Why?
When he was about to use the white sand,
the witch used her blood...
and stained the white sand with his blood.
Why?
Li Wei!
You used your blood to wash him.
I want you to die!
You can't run anymore.
Help!
Don't touch my sister with your dirty hands.
Tear her into pieces.
There's a fire in that room.
If you go five steps further, you'll be poisoned.
There's no cure.
If you don't believe me, try it.
Nonsense.
I don't believe there's such a poison.
Miss Zhou,
I'm sorry to have made you fall down the mountain.
Let me go.
I don't want to die.
This is just one step.
You still have four steps.
Okay.
If you catch Li Wei's woman,
I'll let go of your sister.
No! Let my sister go!
No!
I'll give you one hour.
If you don't catch Li Wei's woman,
I'll let go of your sister.
Wait for me here.
I'll be right back.
You don't look like a bad person.
Tell me.
Why did you kill Yu Li?
To save my sister, I had no choice.
What do we do now?
Help him up.
I had to follow my master's order.
Since you've got a heart,
please go back and report to your master.
You report to your master.
But I'm dead.
What are you doing?
It's not that I don't want to teach you.
It's that I don't believe you.
We're really Jin Da Xiong's men.
You have to believe us.
I don't believe in your abilities.
And I have to wait for someone.
Put me down.
If I don't come back in 15 minutes,
you're dead.
I deserve to die with you.
I've got the man you wanted.
Hurry up.
Get that woman out of the carriage.
You're useless.
Get her out of here.
There's a woman inside.
No wonder she hasn't come out for a long time.
You have to realize today
that I was cunning
and you were lucky enough to win.
Put her down.
Although you have super powers,
it's only a matter of time.
The Seven Stars Fist has a history of 2,000 years.
It's the blood of justice.
The Seven Stars Fist is empty.
Greetings, Master.
It's been a long time since we found a human heart.
You two get out of here
and bring back a few more human hearts.
Yes, sir.
Brother Jin, you have to do this for me.
I'll do my best for Shan Cha.
You've done too much.
Shan Cha is my love. I want to save her.
Don't bother.
You need to rest.
Guards.
Yes, sir.
Go and rest.
No one can stop me in this world.
Guards.
Luckily we ran fast.
I was scared to death.
Let's go.
I'm exhausted.
Let's sit here for a while.
Have a good rest.
Ming.
Wait.
What?
Please teach us martial arts.
Yes, teach us martial arts.
Tell us.
Yes.
You want to learn martial arts?
You have to find my master, Brother Li.
Will he teach us?
What if he doesn't?
Don't worry. I'll take care of everything.
Come with me.
Please forgive my brother.
He didn't do it on purpose.
Ming.
Brother.
What should we do?
What's wrong with you?
Please wake up.
Brother Li.
You Li.
Brother, what should we do?
You Li is in great pain.
His condition is getting worse.
You Li.
Bear with it.
You want to find Brother Li?
Why do you want to kill me?
I hate you.
I hate you very much.
I'm in great pain.
This is not the time to learn martial arts.
Brother Li.
Please accept us as your disciples.
We sincerely worship you.
Yes.
Please accept us as your disciples.
Please, Brother Li.
Learning martial arts is just one person.
Learning martial arts is one hundred thousand people.
Tell me.
Is one person more capable...
than one hundred thousand people?
Brother Li.
Please give me some face.
Brother An.
What should we do?
It's not good. It's very good.
Yes.
Do you think you can do it?
Do you know how to do it?
Not only do I know how to do it,
I also want to kill you.
In front of so many people,
do you think you can beat us?
I don't want to lose you.
You underestimate me.
It's not me.
What are you doing?
I'll let you taste the poison.
Before that, I'll ask you to take a bath.
I'll put the poison here.
I'm not that stupid.
I'm trying to save you and all the children.
I'm trying to lure out the violence.
I didn't expect to be caught
so I put the poison here.
I didn't expect you to be so brave at such a young age.
What about the other children?
They're safe in Shandong.
Don't be angry.
I didn't kill them.
Shan Cha.
Get up and take revenge.
Shan Cha, you can't die.
Although I'm used to being sad,
I'm still afraid of being alone.
Shan Cha.
Get up.
Jin Da Xiong,
Shan Cha is your brother.
He can't even save you.
Are you kidding me?
He's him.
I'm me.
Sometimes it's easier to survive
when we use each other.
You didn't save him on purpose.
You wanted to get me, didn't you?
Is this the attitude of a dying man?
You...
I don't want to.
You can't take my heart.
You're finally saved.
You're cruel.
The body you left behind
is finally the only light you have left.
I admire your medical skills.
You're truly unparalleled.
You turned me into a victim of a challenge.
I hate you, Jin Da Xiong.
How did this happen?
Maybe it's because of a woman.
Shan Cha is powerful.
How can he be so powerful?
Let's go.
What's going to happen in this age?
I want to see it with my own eyes.
Let's go.
This is a bad omen.
I'm afraid Shan Cha can't stand it anymore.
I'm going to find the best man
in the world.
Master, it can't be me.
I don't think I'm the best man.
The best man in the world,
besides the master,
I can't think of anyone else.
The master is the best man.
Yes.
Of course I'm the best man.
But...
I have to change my mind for Shan Cha.
Master, whose heart do you want to capture?
Cousin Li.
Capture Cousin Li.
It's not easy to capture Cousin Li.
I'm here.
It's not easy.
Look.
The dead emperor.
Therefore, we must kill him.
The emperor of hell.
Look.
Even the devil has tamed us.
What else is there to be afraid of in this world?
Cousin Li.
I don't know how many times
I've seen you with a light smile on your face.
I just want to ask you
what's on your mind.
But I don't know how to tell you.
I don't know.
I've tried many times
and I want to know something.
But you're more determined than the stone.
I have no other choice.
I don't want to bother you.
I just hope you don't keep the pain in your heart forever.
You won't understand.
If you're willing,
please tell me your thoughts.
I hope I can bring you peace and harmony.
I've been worried about Liulia.
Liulia.
I know she's beautiful and charming.
Zhan Xiu.
Don't be silly.
They're not children, but I think...
Girl.
I'll take care of you like your brother.
She's different from you.
You belong to Liulia.
That's why you have feelings for her.
You won't deny it, will you?
What is it?
To celebrate your health,
I'll give this to you.
Thank you.
It's a small case.
It's still out there.
Look.
It's Liulia.
She's so pretty.
You're right.
Hurry up and hide.
Liulia.
No matter what,
you have to take it.
No.
Why?
Because I can't just take other people's things.
Don't take me for someone else.
If you keep doing this,
I won't talk to you anymore.
Liulia.
You're a fool.
Brother, it's dangerous.
When the sun rises tomorrow,
the Seven Stars will lose their light.
I grant you the power of the Seven Stars.
The Seven Stars,
although they are so powerful,
they are invincible,
and they can defeat anyone.
But,
it's because of the power of the Seven Stars.
If the Seven Stars lose their light,
you will lose your power at the same time.
So, when the sun rises,
don't fight against the enemy.
Don't use your super powers.
Otherwise, the consequences will be dire.
Remember.
My brother went to save Lin Li.
I have a feeling that he can't stand it anymore.
Where did he go?
To hell.
Brother Li.
The power of the Seven Stars is full of justice.
It can save innocent victims.
Brother Li, I beg you to save them.
I...
The power of the Seven Stars is full of justice.
It can save innocent victims.
Brother Li, I beg you to save them.
I...
I can't.
I see.
You are still angry with my brother.
You dare not go.
I will go.
Welcome to Ghost Valley.
Taste the power of the Seven Stars.
The power of the Seven Stars.
I can't do it.
My body is hot.
What's the matter with you two?
Say it.
Master, is Zhan Hua really dead?
He was saved by Brother Li.
What should we do?
What's so great about saving Zhan Hua?
Master's skills are unparalleled.
It's enough for them to watch.
No matter how powerful he is, he is no match for Master.
He will bleed to death.
That's right.
I have an undercover.
Wait and see.
You Li Ya.
Sister, you're up.
Not only am I up, I'm going to kill you.
Sister, what are you going to do?
Isn't that You Li Ya?
You Li Ya.
You Li Ya, you have recovered.
You can stand up.
Come.
Sister.
I've been lying here for a long time.
Can you come with me?
Sure.
Brother Li,
in my coma,
I dreamt of a man with seven stars in his chest.
I was thinking,
in this world, only you have seven stars in your chest.
Can you show me the seven stars in your chest again?
Sure.
Brother Li.
I won't let you off.
Who is he?
Nothing.
The child is outside.
Brother Li,
if I want to ask you for something,
will you give it to me?
I can give you anything you want.
What if I want your heart?
In order to show my loyalty to you,
I can.
Brother Li,
you have to be careful.
I've committed suicide.
Tell me.
Where is your loyalty?
I've committed suicide.
This heartless man
will be stained with your blood.
You should bear the pain for Brother Li.
Sister.
How could this happen?
Wake up.
Your dearest brother is calling you.
My brother is in pain because of you.
But Brother Ren Tianyuan...
I don't know if he saw or heard it.
Sister.
Father told me to take care of you.
But I didn't fulfill my duty.
I'm very ashamed.
I've committed suicide because of you.
It's too late for me to come back.
Now I can only bear the pain for you.
Sister,
I want them to pay for it.
Let's go.
So you're the man who shot the horse.
You have seven wounds on your chest.
I'm the man who shot the horse.
You've destroyed the reputation of Seven Stars Fist.
Seven Stars Fist is still a powerful power.
Power?
Tell you what,
I'm no match for you in any way.
I've killed the man who shot the horse.
I've never met a man with super powers.
Let me kill him.
I'm going to kill you for my sister.
Only then can I get rid of my hatred.
That's the King of Death.
Don't be afraid.
Just follow my orders.
It's very safe.
Let's go.
No.
We're going to hell.
Yes, we're going to save my sister.
But I'm afraid.
Don't be afraid.
As long as I use the Seven Stars Fist,
all the people inside will be dead.
Really?
Don't underestimate people.
Let's go.
Now you can see the truth.
You're not a mortal.
To uphold justice,
I'm going to get rid of you devils.
The only thing I can do
is to kill the King of Death.
You used the Seven Stars Fist.
The Seven Stars Fist?
It's an air flow.
Hey,
look at this kind of thing.
Now you know how powerful my air flow is.
Let me try again.
All the people inside will be dead.
Only a genius like me can do this kind of thing.
Really?
Stop bragging.
You underestimate people.
You don't believe me?
I don't believe you.
I hope your cousin...
Sister!
Sister, where are you?
Sister, we're here to save you.
Brother Li Piao, what's wrong with Sister?
Yulia!
I'm late.
Sister!
Yulia!
This is a piece of cake.
Let me show you the essence of the Seven Stars Fist.
Brother Li Piao!
No one in this world can compete with me.
Brother Li Piao,
you have to be careful.
The Seven Stars Fist is made of the Star of the Bear.
Now it's not only the Sun,
but also the Star of the Bear.
The Seven Stars Fist is made of the Star of the Bear.
It's not good for you.
Now you have to be quiet
and use the Dragon Breath.
I'll save the Seven Stars Fist.
Then you'll be able to regain your powers.
Brother Li Piao,
everything has calmed down.
Yes, we're finally out of harm's way.
Let's go and save Sister.
Let's go.